Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1991-141
  - Nonsense Correspondence, 1/88-8/1989; AD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Nonsense Correspondence, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 4.20.5 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.20.5)
  - Routine Recommendations, 1/88-8/1989; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.20.6)
  - Discipline of Students (Dean's Cases), 9/87-8/88; A 7.2.5 (Box 3, Folder A 7.2.5)
  - Admissions Cases, 9/88-8/1989; AD 8.1.2 (Box 3, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - Eureka Project, 1/84-8/1989; AD 8.12.3 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.12.3)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, and Emeriti, 9/87-8/88; PAD 8.18 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Housing Office, Miscellaneous Reports, 9/84-8/1989; PAD 8.18.1 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.18.1)
  - Fraternities and sororities, 9/83-8/1986; AD 8.18.8 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.18.8)
  - Housing: Students, 9/84-8/1986; AD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.18.11)
  - Housing: Students, 9/84-8/1989; PAD 8.18.11 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.18.11)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, 9/82-8/1989; PAD 8.18.02 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.18.02)
  - Minority Issues, 1/88-12/88; AD 9 (Box 5, Folder AD 9)
  - Minority Issues, 9/88-8/1989; PAD 9 (Box 5, Folder PAD 9)
  - Minority Issues, 9/87-8/88; PAD 9 (Box 5, Folder PAD 9)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 9/87-8/88; AD 10 (Box 5, Folder AD 10)
  - Employee Inquiries and Requests, 9/83-8/1985; PAD 10.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 10.1)
  - Employee Inquiries and Requests, 9/85-8/1986; PAD 10.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (Mosher 1/84 Appeal to Kennedy), 30682; AD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder AD 10.8.10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (Mosher-Primary Correspondence), 1/85-5/1985; AD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder AD 10.8.10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (Mosher-Primary Correspondence), 6/85-10/1985; AD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder AD 10.8.10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (Mosher-Primary Correspondence), 1984-1986; AD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder AD 10.8.10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (Mosher-Primary Correspondence), 1983-1984; AD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder AD 10.8.10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (W. Lammi), 1984-1986; PAD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 10.8.10.1)
  - Grievance Cases (C. Cagnon), 1983-1984; PAD 10.8.10.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 10.8.10.1)
  - Salaries, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 5, Folder PAD 10.8.19)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, 9/85-8/96; AD 11.6 (Box 5, Folder AD 11.6)
  - Business and Finance, 9/87-8/88; PAD 12.2 (Box 6, Folder PAD 12.2)
  - Auditing, 9/82-8/1986; AD 12.4 (Box 6, Folder AD 12.4)
  - Budgets, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.5 (Box 6, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 9/87-8/88; PAD 12.5 (Box 6, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Health and Safety, 9/81-8/88; AD 12.8.1 (Box 6, Folder AD 12.8.1)
  - Health and Safety, 9/82-8/88; PAD 12.8.1 (Box 6, Folder PAD 12.8.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.10.1 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 9/88-8/1989; PAD 12.10.1 (Box 7, Folder PAD 12.10.1)
  - Miscellaneous Gifts, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.10.3/5-1 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-1)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Miscellaneous Foundations, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.10.4 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 9/87-8/88; AD 12.10.4/130 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.4/130)
  - Corporations, 9/87-8/88; AD 12.10.5 (Box 7, Folder AD 12.10.5)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.14 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/87-8/88; AD 12.14 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/88-8/1989; PAD 12.14 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/87-8/88; PAD 12.14 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14)
  - Facilities Planning, 9/86-8/1987; PAD 12.14.7/29 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14.7/29)
  - Facilities Planning, 9/83-8/1986; PAD 12.14.7/29 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14.7/29)
  - Near West Campus, 1/87-8/88; PAD 12.14.7/31 (Box 8, Folder PAD 12.14.7/31)
  - Tresidder Union Petition, 1986; AD 12.14.7/64 (Box 8, Folder AD 12.14.7/64)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 4/87 -10/1987; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 31837; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library-Academic Senate, 31837; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library-Academic Senate Background Material, 31778; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 9/86-8/1987; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 9/86-8/1989; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Academic Senate Background, 1983-1987; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 1/84-8/1986; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 9/83-8/1986; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 1986; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Petitions, 31747; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 1985; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library Secondary Correspondence, 1984; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 3/84 -12/1984; AD 13.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 30987; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 1/84-2/1984; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 30651; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Meeting With Ed Meese, 30657; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 30621; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 30590; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 7/83-9/1983; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Ronald Reagan Library, 1/83-6/1983; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Comments and Suggestions, 1983; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Secondary Correspondence, 1983; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Preliminary Site Feasibility, 1983; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - RRL-Lists of Documents, 1978-1983; AD 13.9 (Box 10, Folder AD 13.9)
  - Visiting Committee of the SU Libraries, 1/83-8/1987; AD 13.10.5/9 (Box 11, Folder AD 13.10.5/9)
  - Provost's Advisory Group (1 of 3), 9/87 -; PAA 1.1 (Box 11, Folder PAA 1.1)
  - Provost's Advisory Group(2 of 3), 9/87 -; PAA 1.1 (Box 11, Folder PAA 1.1)
  - Provost's Advisory Group (3 of 3), 9/87 -; PAA 1.1 (Box 11, Folder PAA 1.1)
  - Graduate Studies, 9/84-8/1985; PAA 1.13 (Box 11, Folder PAA 1.13)
  - University Fellows, 9/83-8/1986; AA 2.9 (Box 11, Folder AA 2.9)
  - Council of Admin., Dean's UG Studies (CADUS) 9/1987-8/88, PAA 3.2 (Box 11, Folder PAA 3.2)
  - Council of Admin., Dean's UG Studies (CADUS) 9/88-8/89, PAA 3.2 (Box 12, Folder PAA 3.2)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, 9/86-8/1987; AA 4.1.12 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.12)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, 9/82-8/1987; PAA 4.1.12 (Box 12, Folder PAA 4.1.12)
  - Department of Economics, 1/79-8/1987; PAA 4.1.20 (Box 12, Folder PAA 4.1.20)
  - Center for Economic Policy, 9/83-8/1987; PAA 4.1.20/1 (Box 12, Folder PAA 4.1.20/1)
  - Athletic Department, 9/88-8/1989; AA 4.1.30 (Box 12, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Physics Visiting Committee, 9/82-8/1986; PAA 4.1.33 (Box 12, Folder PAA 4.1.33)
  - School of Engineering, 9/88-8/1989; PAA 4.4 (Box 13, Folder PAA 4.4)
  - School of Medicine, 9/88-8/1989; AA 4.6 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 9/88-8/1989; PAA 4.6 (Box 13, Folder PAA 4.6)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/88-8/1989; PAA 4.9 (Box 13, Folder PAA 4.9)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/88-8/1989; AA 4.9 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Hoover Board of Overseers, 9/88-8/1989; AA 4.9.1 (Box 13, Folder AA 4.9.1)
  - Hoover Board of Overseers, 9/87-8/1989; PAA 4.9.1 (Box 13, Folder PAA 4.9.1)
  - Center for Rsrch. in International Studies 9/83-8/89, PAA 4.10 (Box 14, Folder PAA 4.10)
  - Center for Intern. Secur. and Arms Control, 9/87-8/1989; AA 4.10.6 (Box 14, Folder AA 4.10.6)
  - Stanford Libraries, 9/87-8/1989; PAA 4.12 (Box 14, Folder PAA 4.12)
  - Research Library Group, 9/86-8/1987; AA 4.12.1 (Box 14, Folder AA 4.12.1)
  - RLG/RLIN, 9/81-8/88; PAA 4.12.1 (Box 14, Folder PAA 4.12.1)
  - School of Law, 9/87-8/88; AA 4.15 (Box 14, Folder AA 4.15)
  - School of Law, 9/82-8/88; PAA 4.15 (Box 15, Folder PAA 4.15)
  - Stanford Hospital, 9/88-1/1989; AA 4.17 (Box 15, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital, 2/89-5/1989; AA 4.17 (Box 15, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital, 6/89-8/1989; AA 4.17 (Box 15, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital, 9/88-8/1989; PAA 4.17 (Box 15, Folder PAA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital General Members (10 Files), 2/84-8/88; PAA 4.17.1 (Box 16, Folder PAA 4.17.1)
  - SU Hospital Finance Committee, 3/86-9/1986; AA 4.17.1 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.17.1)
  - Endowed Chairs, Professorships, 9/83-8/1989; PAA 10 (Box 17, Folder PAA 10)
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 5/89-8/1989; ST 1 (Box 17, Folder ST 1)
  - Dean of the Chapel, Dean of Chapel Search, 1984-1986; PAA 1.8 (Box 17, Folder PAA 1.8)
  - Participation in Politics, Policy, 1984-1988; AD 7.13 (Box 17, Folder AD 7.13)
  - Dean/Students Case Numbers, PAD 7.25 (Box 17, Folder PAD 7.25)
  - Affirmative Action Office, 3/87-12/1987; AD 9.6 (Box 17, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Academic Information Center, 1982-1988; PAA 1.6 (Box 17, Folder PAA 1.6)
  - Undergraduate Education, 1982-1988; PAA 1.12 (Box 17, Folder PAA 1.12)
  - Disc.-Student Cases, 1983-1986; PAD 7.2.7 (Box 17, Folder PAD 7.2.7)
  - Graduate Studies, 12/82-11/8; PAA 1.13.2 (Box 17, Folder PAA 1.13.2)
  - Center for Intern. Secur. and Arms Control, 9/82-8/1987; AA 4.10.6 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.10.6)
  - 0 (Box not specified)
  - Public Service Center, 9/88-8/1989; ST 3.29 (Box 18, Folder ST 3.29)
  - PSC: Faculty Steering Committee, 9/87-8/1989; ST 3.29 (Box 18, Folder ST 3.29)
  - PSC: Overseas Development Network, 9/88-8/1989; ST 3.29 (Box 18, Folder ST 3.29)
  - PSC: Gardner Fellowship, 1/84-8/88; ST 3.29/1 (Box 18, Folder ST 3.29/1)
  - Freshman Class, 9/79-8/1989; ST 5.3 (Box 18, Folder ST 5.3)
  - Outside Organizations (Six Files, with the exception of 9/89), 9/88-11/1989; 0 1 (Box 18, Folder 0 1)
  - Educational Groups, 4/84-7/1989; 0 3 (Box 19, Folder 0 3)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 9/88-8/1989; 0 3.1 (Box 19, Folder 0 3.1)
  - American Council on Education, 9/86-8/1989; 0 3.8 (Box 19, Folder 0 3.8)
  - Nat. Assoc. of Indepen. Colleges and Univ., 9/81-8/1989; 0 3.10 (Box 19, Folder 0 3.10)
  - Coll. Entrance Exam. Board, 9/84-8/1989; 0 3.25 (Box 19, Folder 0 3.25)
  - Institute of Medicine, 9/85-8/1987; 0 3.42 (Box 19, Folder 0 3.42)
  - Institute of Medicine, 9/87-8/1989; 0 3.43 (Box 19, Folder 0 3.43)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 9/87-8/1989; 0 3.43 (Box 20, Folder 0 3.43)
  - NCAA, 12/84-8/1989; 0 3.44 (Box 20, Folder 0 3.44)
  - Pacific Ten Conference Part 1, 8/85-8/1989; 0 3.47 (Box 20, Folder 0 3.47)
  - Pacific Ten Conference Part 2, 8/85-8/1989; 0 3.47 (Box 20, Folder 0 3.47)
  - Pacific Ten Conference Part 3, 8/85-8/1989; 0 3.47 (Box 20, Folder 0 3.47)
  - Other Universities, 2/89-8/1989; 0 8 (Box 20, Folder 0 8)
  - AAU, 9/88-8/1989; 0 8.7 (Box 20, Folder 0 8.7)
  - Harvard University, 9/82-8/88; O 8.23 (Box 21, Folder O 8.23)
  - University of California, 9/81-8/1989; O 8.43 (Box 21, Folder O 8.43)
  - Western Assoc. of Schools and Colleges, 9/83-8/1989; O 8.52 (Box 21, Folder O 8.52)
  - Sponsored Projects, 9/88-8/1989; R 1 (Box 21, Folder R 1)
  - Committee on Research, 9/88-8/1989; R 1.2 (Box 21, Folder R 1.2)
  - Vice Provost for Research, 9/82-8/1989; R 1.1 (Box 22, Folder R 1.1)
  - Senate-Academic Council, 9/88-8/1989; C 2 (Box 22, Folder C 2)
  - Senate of the Academic Council Corres., 9/83-8/1989; C 2.1 (Box 22, Folder C 2.1)
  - Advisory Board, 9/88-8/1989; C 3 (Box 22, Folder C 3)
  - Steering Committee, 9/88-8/1989; C 4.1 (Box 22, Folder C 4.1)
  - Faculty and Staff Benefits Committee, 9/82-8/1989; C 6.5 (Box 22, Folder C 6.5)
  - Human Resources Council, 9/88-8/1989; C 6.5.1 (Box 23, Folder C 6.5.1)
  - University committee on Minority Issues, 6/86-8/1989; C 6.9.2 (Box 23, Folder C 6.9.2)
  - California State Government, 9/81-8/1989; G 1.2 (Box 23, Folder G 1.2)
  - United States Government Relations, 9/87-8/1989; G 3 (Box 23, Folder G 3)
  - Federal Legislation, 9/86-8/1987; G 3.1 (Box 23, Folder G 3.1)
  - National Science Foundation, 9/87-8/88; G 3.19 (Box 24, Folder G 3.19)
  - National Science Foundation, 9/88-8/1989; G 3.19 (Box 24, Folder G 3.19)
  - U.S.S.R., 9/84-8/1989; G 5.1 (Box 24, Folder G 5.1)
  - South Africa, 9/87-8/88; G 5.3 (Box 24, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa: Corporations:/Divest/, 9/86-8/1987; G 5.3 (Box 24, Folder G 5.3)
  - Sullivan Prin./Corresp. w/Board, 9/86-8/1987; G 5.3 (Box 24, Folder G 5.3)
  - Notes, D.K.'s South Africa Trip, 31625; G 5.3 (Box 24, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa: Corporations: Divest./Sullivan Prin./Corresp. w/Board, 1985-8/1986; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa: Other Univs. and Govt. Agencies/SA Fellows-Exchange Trip DK, 12-1985-9-19; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - Symposium on South Africa, 31843; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa University-Corporate Mtg. Hoover House, 31286; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa-Petitions, G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa, South Africa News from Investment Respons. Task Force, 1986; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa-Articles and Reports, G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - Report on Johnson Foundation/Brookings Institution Conference on South Africa, 31323; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa Divestiture-Correspondence, 6/1/1985-12/31/; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa Divestiture and Articles, 12/84-5/31/; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - South Africa Divestiture-Correspondence and Articles, 31413; G 5.3 (Box 25, Folder G 5.3)
  - Board of Trustees, 9/88-8/1989; B 1 (Box 26, Folder B 1)
  - BoT: Agendas and Pre-agendas, 9/85-8/1987; B 13.3 (Box 26, Folder B 13.3)
  - BoT: Agendas and Pre-agendas, 9/87-8/1989; B 13.3 (Box 26, Folder B 13.3)
  - Trustee Committees, 9/83-8/1989; B 14 (Box 26, Folder B 14)
  - Committee on Nominations, 9/82-8/1989; B 14.7 (Box 27, Folder B 14.7)
  - BoT: Select Committee on Invest. Respons. (1981) part 1, 9/87-8/1989; B 14.10 (Box 27, Folder B 14.10)
  - BoT: Select Committee on Invest. Respons. (1981), part 2; B 14.10 (Box 27, Folder B 14.10)
  - Presidential Chrons (12 months), 1987 (Box 28)
  - Centennial, 1988; AD 1.3 (Box 1A, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Centennial, 1989; AD 1.3 (Box 1A, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Centennial 1989-1991, [1] (Box 1B, Folder [1])
  - Centennial Campaign Communications Plan, 1985-86, [2] (Box 1B, Folder [2])
  - Centennial-prospectus, 1984-1985, [3] (Box 1B, Folder [3])
  - Fundraising in the '80s, by Donald Kennedy and Joel P. Smith, [4] (Box 1B, Folder [4])
  - Centennial Campaign Dev. Ofc. Task Force on Centennial, 1983-1987, [5] (Box 1B, Folder [5])
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1992-179
  - Centennial, 1990; AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Centennial (1 of 2), 1990; AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Centennial (2 of 2), 1990; AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - President's Resources Group, AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Honor Code/Fundamental Standard, 1988-90; AD 3.10 (Box 1, Folder AD 3.10)
  - Univ. Calendar, Holidays, 1985; PAD 3.21 (Box 1, Folder PAD 3.21)
  - Administrative Council, 1989; AD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Administrative Council, 1990; PAD 4.12 (Box 1, Folder PAD 4.12)
  - University Cabinet, 1990; AD 4.13 (Box 1, Folder AD 4.13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1/1990-6/1990; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 7/1990-12/1990; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Condolence Letters, 1988-89; AD 4.20.2 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.2)
  - Nonsense Correspondence, 1988/1989; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Nonsense Correspondence, 1990; AD 4.20.5 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.5)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1979-89; PAD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder PAD 4.20.6)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1989; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.20.6)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1990; AD 4.20.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.20.6)
  - Complaints, 1987-90; AD 4.20.7 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.20.7)
  - Public Affairs Office, 1988-90; AD 4.22 (Box 3, Folder AD 4.22)
  - Legal Problems and Services, 1988-90; AD 7 (Box 3, Folder AD 7)
  - Discipline of Students, 1988-90; AD 7.2.5 (Box 3, Folder AD 7.2.5)
  - Admissions Office, 1988-90; AD 8.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.1)
  - Admissions Cases, 9/1989-1990; AD 8.1.2 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - Career Planning and Placement, 1982-89; AD 8.7 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.7)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1982-87; PAD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.8)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 1988-90; AD 8.8 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.8)
  - Policy on Discrimination, 1986/1987; PAD 8.8.3 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.8.3)
  - Exchange Programs, 1986; PAD 8.10 (Box 4, Folder PAD 8.10)
  - Stanford in Washington, DC, 1988-90; AD 8.10.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.10.1)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies Program, 1983-88; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.11)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies Program, 1989/1990; AD 8.11 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.11)
  - Stanford Program in Berlin, 1983-90; AD 8.11.4/2 (Box 4, Folder AD 8.11.4/2)
  - Stanford Center in Japan, 1986/1987; PAD 8.11.6 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.11.6)
  - 0, 1988-90; AD 8.11.6 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.11.6)
  - Financial Aids, 1983-1986; PAD 8.12 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.12)
  - 0, 1988-90; AD 8.12 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.12)
  - Student Loans, 1987; PAD 8.12.1 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.12.1)
  - Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, Housing, 9/88-1989; PAD 8.18 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - 11 11, 1990; PAD 8.18 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18)
  - Buck House/Estate, 1982-87; PAD 8.18.4 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18.4)
  - Escondido Village, 1984/1985; PAD 8.18.7 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18.7)
  - Fraternities/Sororities, 1983-87; PAD 8.18.8 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18.8)
  - Student Housing, 1988-90; AD 8.18.11 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18.11)
  - Domestic Partners, 1989/1990; AD 8.18.11 (Box 5, Folder AD 8.18.11)
  - Residence Halls/Staff, 1982-87; PAD 8.18.12 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18.12)
  - Residential Education, 1986/1987; PAD 8.18.13 (Box 5, Folder PAD 8.18.13)
  - Registrar, 1982-87; PAD 8.21 (Box 6, Folder PAD 8.21)
  - Minority Issues, 1989/1990; AD 9 (Box 6, Folder AD 9)
  - Black Affairs, 1983-88; PAD 9.1 (Box 6, Folder PAD 9.1)
  - Chicano Affairs, 1984-87; PAD 9.2 (Box 6, Folder PAD 9.2)
  - Affirmative Action/Multicultural Devl., 1988-90; AD 9.3 (Box 6, Folder AD 9.3)
  - Affirmative Action for Women, 1983; AD 9.6 (Box 6, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 1987; PAD 10 (Box 6, Folder PAD 10)
  - Employee and Personnel Relations, 1988-90; AD 10 (Box 6, Folder AD 10)
  - Employment Inquiries and Request, 9/1987-88; AD 10.1 (Box 7, Folder AD 10.1)
  - Employment Inquiries and Request, 1989/1990; AD 10.1 (Box 7, Folder AD 10.1)
  - Staff Development Programs, 1985-87; PAD 10.2 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.2)
  - Human Resources Programs, PAD 10.4 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.4)
  - Policy: Appointment of Lectures and Other Short-term Teachers, 1983-87; PAD 10.6 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.6)
  - Child Care, 1983-87; PAD 10.7.5 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.7.5)
  - The Stanford Center for the Study of Family, Child and Youth, PAD 10.7.6 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.7.6)
  - United Stanford Employees, 1984/1985; PAD 10.7.8 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.7.8)
  - Personnel Policies, PAD 10.8 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.8)
  - Faculty/Staff Fringe Benefits, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.9 (Box 7, Folder PAD 10.8.9)
  - Faculty/Staff Fringe Benefits, 1988-90; AD 10.8.9 (Box 7, Folder AD 10.8.9)
  - Faculty/Staff Grievance Procedures, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.10 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.10)
  - Grievance Hearings: Cases, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.10/1 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.10/1)
  - Possible Grievances, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.10/2 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.10/2)
  - Grievances: Student/Faculty on Academic Matters, 1983-85; PAD 10.8.10/3 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.10/3)
  - Leaves of Absence/Faculty and Staff, 1969; PAD 10.8.15 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.15)
  - Retirement, 9/1981-87; PAD 10.8.17 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.17)
  - Retirement, 1988/1989; AD 10.8.17 (Box 8, Folder AD 10.8.17)
  - Early Retirement, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.17/1 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.17/1)
  - TIAA/CREF and Prudential, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.17/3 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.17/3)
  - Salaries, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.19 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.19)
  - Policy: Travel, 1983-87; PAD 10.8.21 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.21)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan, 1983-86; PAD 10.8.22 (Box 8, Folder PAD 10.8.22)
  - Archives, 1982-86; PAD 11.1 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.1)
  - Food Services, 1983-87; PAD 11.3 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.3)
  - Services Operations, 1984-86; PAD 11.4 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.4)
  - Hazardous Waste Disposal, 9/1983-87; PAD 11.4.1 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.4.1)
  - Police Services, 1983-87; PAD 11.6 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.6)
  - Assault/Sexual (Rape), 1979; AD 11.6 (Box 9, Folder AD 11.6)
  - Office of Public Events, 1983-87; PAD 11.7 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.7)
  - Commencement, 1986/1987; PAD 11.7.2 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.7.2)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1983-87; PAD 11.7.2/1 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.7.2/1)
  - Dedications: Computation Center, 1983-86; PAD 11.7.4 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.7.4)
  - Founders Day, 1983-87; PAD 11.7.6 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.7.6)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1983-87; PAD 11.7.7 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.7.7)
  - Publications Service Communication, 1984-87; PAD 11.8 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8)
  - Copyright Policy, 1983-85; PAD 11.8.1 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.1)
  - Privacy of Records, 1983; PAD 11.8.3 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.3)
  - Stanford News Service, 1983-86; PAD 11.8.4 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.4)
  - Policy: Solicitation on Campus, 1982; PAD 11.8.8 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.8)
  - Stanford University Press, 1983-87; PAD 11.8.9 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.9)
  - Stanford University Press, 1988-90; AD 11.8.9 (Box 9, Folder AD 11.8.9)
  - Surveys Studies and Questionnaires, 1983-87; PAD 11.8.10 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.10)
  - Surveys Studies and Questionnaires, 1983-87; AD 11.8.10 (Box 9, Folder AD 11.8.10)
  - Stanford Publications, Miscellaneous, 1983-87; PAD 11.8.11 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.11)
  - Television Instructional Network, 1983-87; PAD 11.8.13 (Box 9, Folder PAD 11.8.13)
  - Business and Finance, 9/88-8/1989; AD 12.2 (Box 9, Folder AD 12.2)
  - VP for Business and Finance, 1983; PAD 12.2.1 (Box 9, Folder PAD 12.2.1)
  - VP for Business and Finance, 9/1986-8/88; PAD 12.2.1 (Box 9, Folder PAD 12.2.1)
  - Controller's Office, 1983-87; PAD 12.2.2 (Box 10, Folder PAD 12.2.2)
  - Controller's Office/VP Business and Fin., 1988-90; AD 12.2.2 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.2.2)
  - Treasurer, 1986/1987; PAD 12.3 (Box 10, Folder PAD 12.3)
  - Treasurer, 1988; AD 12.3 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.3)
  - Treasurer, 1989; AD 12.3 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.3)
  - Treasurer, 1990; AD 12.3 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.3)
  - Auditing, 1988-90; AD 12.4 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.4)
  - Budget Group, 1988; PAD 12.5 (Box 10, Folder PAD 12.5)
  - Budgets, 1989; AD 12.5 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.5)
  - 11 11, 1990; AD 12.5 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Health and Safety, 1988; AD 12.8.1 (Box 10, Folder AD 12.8.1)
  - Office of Development, 1989; AD 12.10.1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Office of Development, 1990; AD 12.10.1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - Gifts Miscellaneous, 1983-89; AD 12.10.3/5/1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5/1)
  - Gifts Miscellaneous, 1990; AD 12.10.3/5-1 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-1)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1983-89; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Carnegie Corporation, 1990; AD 12.10.3/5-10 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-10)
  - Glenmede Trust, 1983-87; AD 12.10.3/5-26 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-26)
  - Glenmede Trust, 1988-90; AD 12.10.3/5-26 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-26)
  - Prospective Donors, 1965-86; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - Prospective Donors, 1987; AD 12.10.3/12 (Box 11, Folder AD 12.10.3/12)
  - IBM, 1983-90; AD 12.10.3/5-51 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-51)
  - Miscellaneous Foundations, 1983-89; AD 12.10.4 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4)